nextdesks.com 2014-12-14

# NextDesk Privacy Policy | NextDesk

## NextDesk Privacy Policy

Please carefully review this privacy policy before using this site. Any use of this website creates a binding agreement to comply with these terms and conditions. If you do not agree to these terms, please exit this site immediately.

This Web site is the responsibility of NextDesks.com (NextDesk). If you have questions regarding the Agreement or the practices of NextDesk, please contact us by e-mail or regular mail.

## The NextDesk/NextDesk Commitment to Privacy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy NextDesk provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, NextDesk has made it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. The Information NextDesk Collects: This notice applies to all information collected or submitted at www.NextDeskUV.com. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:

Name

Address

Email Address

Phone number

Credit/Debit Card Information

On some pages, you can submit information about other people. For example, if you order a gift online and want it sent directly to the recipient, you will need to submit the recipient's address. In this circumstance, the types of personal information collected are:

Name

Address

Phone number

## The Way NextDesk Uses Information:

NextDesk uses the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. NextDesk does not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. NextDesk uses the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to ship the product and to confirm delivery. NextDesk does not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. NextDesk uses return email addresses to answer email that we receive. Such addresses are not shared with outside parties.

NextDesk uses non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our NextDeskUV.com site and to share with advertisers. For example, NextDesk may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our NextDeskbsite, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but NextDesk would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals. Finally, NextDesk never uses or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

## Our Commitment To Data Security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, NextDesk has put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information NextDesk.com collects online.

## Our Commitment to Children's Privacy:

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, NextDesk never collects or maintain information at NextDeskUV.com from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our NextDesk.com is structured to attract anyone under 13. How You Can Access or Correct Your Information

You can access all your personally identifiable information that NextDesk collects online and maintain by calling us and verifying your identitiy. NextDesk.com uses this procedure to better safeguard your information. You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. To protect your privacy and security, NextDesk will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

## NextDesk's Right to Contact User.

NextDesk reserves the right to contact site visitors regarding account status and changes to the subscriber agreement, privacy policy, or any other policies or agreements relevant to site visitors.

## NextDesk's Right to Change Privacy Policy.

NextDesk reserves the right to change this policy at any time by notifying visitors of the existence and location of the new or revised privacy policy.

## How To Contact Us

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please send contact us by visting our contact us page
